<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="edu.vanderbilt.riaps.system.feature"
      label="RIAPS Domain Specific Modeling Environment"
      version="0.9.7.qualifier"
      provider-name="Institute for Software Integrated Systems, Vanderbilt University">

   <description url="https://riaps.isis.vanderbilt.edu/">
      These plugins install the Integrated Development Environment Plugins for Resilience Information Architecture Platform for Smart Grid.
   </description>

   <license url="">
      Copyright (c) 2017, Vanderbilt University.  
Developed with the sponsorship of the Advanced Research Projects Agency – Energy (ARPA-E) of the Department of Energy.
 
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this data, including any software or 
models in source or binary form, specifications, algorithms, and documentation (collectively &apos;the Data&apos;), to deal in
the Data without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, 
sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Data, and to permit persons to whom the Data is furnished to do so, subject to 
the following conditions:
 
The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Data.
 
THE DATA IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES 
OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS, SPONSORS, DEVELOPERS, CONTRIBUTORS, OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE DATA OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE DATA.
   </license>

   <url>
      <discovery label="Xtext plugin installation site" url="http://download.eclipse.org/modeling/tmf/xtext/updates/composite/releases/"/>
   </url>

   <plugin
         id="edu.vanderbilt.riaps.system"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.vanderbilt.riaps.system.ide"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.vanderbilt.riaps.system.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.vanderbilt.riaps.app"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.vanderbilt.riaps.app.ide"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

   <plugin
         id="edu.vanderbilt.riaps.app.ui"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
